Problem Statement:

Consider an algorithm that takes as input a positive integer n. If n is even, 
the algorithm divides it by two, and if n is odd, the algorithm multiplies it by 
three and adds one. The algorithm repeats this, until n is one. For example, 
the sequence for n=3 is as follows:
3→10→5→16→8→4→2→1

Your task is to simulate the execution of the algorithm for a given value of n.

Input

The only input line contains an integer n.

Output

Print a line that contains all values of n during the algorithm.

Constraints
1≤n≤106
Example

Input:
3

Output:
3 10 5 16 8 4 2 1


Approach:

while(n!=1)
    {
        if(n%2==0)
        {
            n=n/2;
            printf("%d ",n); //for the even number
        }
        else
        {
            n=(3*n)+1;
            printf("%d ",n); // for the odd number
        }
    }
